hikarabita kotoba wo tsunai de
connecting old words that have been used up
soredemo bokura shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dake na no
I just want to convey my simple thoughts
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi no kaze wa
that day's faint wind blows away
kinou no haikyo ni uchi sutete
at the castle ruins of yesterday
kimi to warau ima wo ikiru no da
I'll laugh with you and live for the moment
soredemo ano dekigoto ga kimi wo kurushimeru daro
still that incident will continue to trouble you, right?
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
that's why it must be good-bye
konomama nanimo nokorazu ni anata to wakachiau dake
leaving nothing behind, let us share what is left
yagate bokura wa sore ga subetee dato kigatsuite
in time, we'll realize that it was everything
kanashimi wa hoo wo tsutatte namida no kawa ni naru dake
and sadness will touch our cheeks, creating a river of tears
yureru omoi wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeau no yo
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex and melting away
{The Leaf's Handsome
{Devil Attacks!
Crap!
No matter how many times you try...
it's the same!
I'll acknowledge you.
You're not only sharp...
You're also very determined...
In addition, I'm nice too...
Striking a helpless woman
is against my policy...
But however I look at it,
you don't have the feel of
a helpless woman...
in your case!
Don't be getting full of yourself
just because you released
the Genjutsu, you idiot...!
She's still not completely bound.
Damn it...
I can't lose!
A little more...
What Chakra she has?!
Even if I bind her
at point-blank range
she still pushes back...
But I'll get hammered
for sure if I let go now.
After all, I just have to put this
to rest with this Jutsu.
Hang in there, Akamaru!
Damn it... What's going on?!
Damn it!
One more... to go...
This guy's crazy strong...
Not a single hit with that
many shadow clones...
It's about time...
I've been eagerly waiting.
Orochimaru-sama's ambition...
The first step...
Sasuke...
Sasuke! What're you doing
with these guys?!
Come on! We're going home now!
Sasuke...
Hey...
Should we go home?
Yeah!
We've both made it to the top!
I want to fight you too.
Hey... We're going home.
Everyone's worried about you.
So...
Sasuke!
Please. Bring back Sasuke-kun...!
You can hear my voice, can't you?!
Wait, Sasuke!
It's futile...
Die.
Who're you?
The rejuvenated...
Leaf Village's Handsome Devil...
Rock Lee!
B-Bushy Brow...?
Bushy Brow, you!
What about your body...?
More importantly, Naruto-kun.
Go get Sasuke-kun.
But... you...
Please leave this person to me!
This guy's... good...
Bushy Brow! Be careful!
He uses his own bones to attack.
Bones... you say...?
He's crazy strong...
What're you doing?!
Please go quickly!
Naruto-kun...
You also promised Sakura-san
with a "nice-guy pose", right?!
I'll bring back Sasuke no matter what!
It's a promise of a lifetime!
This person... I'll beat him!
I promise!
Right!
I won't let you!
Die.
Please don't ignore me!
Oh...
Bushy Brow...
You don't have the time
to be inattentive!
Good response!
However...
If Sasuke is inside that coffin...
It'd be totally impossible to take them
on with a Genin team...
We Jonin are in this plight...
We should organize a special team
and send them out for backup.
We can't do that...
Ever since Orochimaru's attack,
the Leaf is currently losing strength
as a great land.
You understand that the Jonin
and Chunin are being totally mobilized
in order to take out possible domestic
and international dangers.
Even if the Sharingan were to fall
into Orochimaru's hands...
We should now prioritize
avoiding war with other lands.
But... I'm sure the Orochimaru situation
isn't a problem that can be deferred forever.
If he regains power...
He'll promptly attack again...
I know...
I'm not such a fool.
I was sure to think about it and
measures have already been taken.
In here!
What's wrong, Guy?
You're on the brink of exhaustion.
Did something happen
on your mission?
No... I took care of the mission
and ran back with all of my might...
More importantly...
Lee! What happened with
Lee's surgery?!
It was a success.
He can start training starting tomorrow
if it's just for Jutsu.
Well, bed rest for a while
would be best though.
Th-There's trouble, Fifth Hokage-sama.
Rock Lee is gone!
No!
Next will be the end.
Damn it... Last night while
I treated Genma and Raido?
Lee...
That fool... He went after them.
And... he must've been really flustered...
He took my bottle of alcohol for
a bottle of medicine by mistake...
SAKE
Alcohol?!
Uh... Uh-oh...
What's wrong, Guy?
Actually when Lee drinks even
a little bit of alcohol...
Things get... so messy...
Get so messy?
Severe Leaf Hurricane!
He's agile... My kicks don't hit.
You're flexible to
a surprising extent...
And you make unique movements, eh?
You're too... straightforward.
It's over...
Please wait!
I'm sorry.
It's about time for my medicine!
I have to be sure to drink it so...
Excuse me a moment.
I've always disliked medicine.
It... happened before when
I took him to a restaurant
to celebrate his acquisition
of the "Hidden Lotus."
Lee mistook my alcohol for water...
As soon as he drank just
a small cup...
of the alcohol things got ugly...
Got ugly...?
After a silence that was like
right before a storm...
The moment I realized it
the restaurant...
had gotten all messed up...
Medicine always tastes stran...
What...? What did this guy drink?
Messed up?
What do you mean?
He's terribly....!
Tsunade-sama... Lee goes into
an incredible drunken frenzy!
Huh...?
Who the hell are you?! Hey!
Jeez, who are you anyway?
Acting cool... So irritating...
Hence he's a natural user of...
Drunken Fist!
Sasuke!
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
boku nanka ga shaberi kaketara meiwaku ni omou ka na
would you think it was a bother if I approached you?
sonna fuan o kakaete yuuki o dashite mita yo
despite my doubts I worked up my courage
umaku shaberenai boku no fukiyou na hanashi
my clumsy attempts with words
kimi wa mimi o sorasazu ni chanto kiite kureta yo
you listened without turning away
sore dake de boku wa ukarete shimau no sa
no wonder I get carried away by you
dakedo kimi wa boku nante nantomo omottenai yo ne
but you don't feel anything for me do you?
setsunai yo
I feel so sad
dakedo
but...
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
In my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
You fell for it, didn't you?!
How about my strategy?
This is the Shinobi Secret
of reading the double bluff!
Guy-sensei! I did it once again!
Yeah!
But what's this?!
The world is oddly...
f-floating
and I've no inclination of losing!
Next time:
"The Beast Explodes! Burst, Blow and Break Through!"